[church bells ringing]
Good morning, sisters.
Let us pray.
[engine revving]
Our Father, who art in heaven...
[rock song playing]
...but deliver us from evil.
[Mother Superior] For thine is
the kingdom, the power...
[coughs]
...forever and ever. Amen.
[Mother Superior] You wanted
to speak to us, Mr Shelby?
Yep.
-All of us?
-Yep.
At 6:30 in the morning?
[Tommy] Yes.
We don't smoke in here.
Well, I fucking do.
Nor do we use language.
Nor do we find fault in the innocent.
Yet, you do.
You fucking do.
May I ask what this meeting is about?
The Grace Shelby Foundation
is the biggest single source of funding
for this charitable institution
devoted to the care of the orphaned girls
of South Birmingham, yeah?
For which we give thanks.
Uh-huh.
I have a temper similar to the one
described in that report.
Yet, unlike you,
I wait until I'm matched in size.
Whose report?
The testimony of children.
Who have they spoken to?
You'd have them only speak to God.
[Mother Superior] God be their witness.
There is God,
and there are the Peaky Blinders.
This is Sparkhill, we're in Small Heath.
We're much, much closer at hand than God.
And we have heard terrible things.
We have, in this place,
children of the worst sort.
They lie as easily as breathe.
[Polly] You had a child half black.
You made her wash with a different soap.
Mr Shelby, your own sins are legend.
[Tommy] Our sins.
Our sins against the beating of children
with bricks and hoses.
Our sins...
against the black child who hanged herself
for fear of your temper.
-[Mother Superior] I do not see how--
-You do not see...
Now put 'em on.
Put 'em on your face
or it'll be your eyes that are broken.
And please don't imagine
that I won't use this minute to do it
or that I am afraid of your prayers
or your crosses.
You see the world broken.
Like those beaten children will.
[Tommy] Now look at me.
Look at me.
[breathes deeply]
Look at me!
Funding withdrawn.
All children to be
taken into our own institutions.
You have no say in where the children--
[Polly] If I come for you,
and I still might yet decide
to come for you,
I will wear high heels
so you can hear my approach
on the cobblestones
and have time to repent.
[church bells ringing]
You listen for my footsteps.
Happy birthday, Pol.
You grow grand in the horse shit, Pol.
Curly, pour some beer, eh?
The train to London leaves in an hour.
Arthur, Michael, you're coming with me.
Tommy, I have to take Gina
to the hospital today.
A week ago, one of our most trusted men
was killed by Jimmy McCavern.
The man we're going to speak to in London
is establishing a relationship
with Jimmy McCavern.
So, cancel your appointments,
and Ada can take Gina to the hospital.
'Cause that's what women do.
[scoffs]
Clean that shit off your shoes
before you get in me car, eh?
Michael, they will give it and give it
until your case is proven,
and then they'll take it.
From you, but mainly from me.
Polly, you go to the hospital
and speak to Aberama Gold.
You tell him there is a strategy in place
to avenge the death of his son,
so not to do anything rash.
And take with you
the heartfelt condolences
of the whole family.
Why me?
Because Aberama Gold is in love with you.
He even got an haircut.
And the smell of your perfume
might help ease his pain.
Tommy, I'm 45 years old today.
Forty-five years old
and still breaking hearts, eh?
-[Arthur] Yeah.
-To Polly.
-Polly Gray. Hmm?
-Right.
Polly.
Happy birthday, Pol, yeah.
Curly, organise a wagon
to take Bonnie Gold's soul to heaven.
Isiah, fetch his boxing gloves
from the gym to burn with his body.
Michael, turn the Bentley around.
We have a train to catch.
[chuckling]
And don't forget to wipe
that shit off your shoes, eh?
Just start up the car and drive.
♪ There ain't no grave ♪
♪ Can hold my body down ♪
[Michael] So, what's the strategy?
You can smile. And you, don't smile.
♪ There ain't no grave ♪
♪ Can hold my body down ♪
Nice.
Very nice, Tom.
Hmm.
Although, I must say, I thought
your office would be bigger than this.
It will be.
Michael, you sit.
Arthur, you stand by the window.
So, who we meetin'?
[Tommy] The man we're about to meet
is the minister
for the Duchy of Lancaster.
He is also deputy
to the Chancellor of the Exchequer
and Cabinet adviser
to the Prime Minister of Great Britain.
You've both met bad men before.
The man we're about to meet is the devil.
[phone ringing]
Yep. Send him in.
[exhales heavily]
I never seem to get to meet you
without your family.
I understand you know a man
called Jimmy McCavern.
May I take a cigarette?
Please.
Who on earth is Jimmy McCavern?
Over the last 12 months,
you've been making approaches
to various men across the country
who you think might be able to
help you in your cause.
McCavern is one of these men.
He runs the East Glasgow shipyards.
He killed an associate of mine.
I want to know what your strategy is.
That one's your brother, yes?
[Michael] Yes.
And I'm his business adviser.
We would like to talk business.
Michael.
Michael Gray.
You lost all your cousin's money
in America playing the fool.
[tutting]
A night club in Detroit
called the Gladiator is your regular.
You lost the money...
and found a wife there.
And poor old Arthur Shelby,
standing there at the window,
-is afraid his wife will never return.
-[wood creaking]
My spies tell me she's been seen
with another man.
Arthur... Arthur.
[in Romani] His time will come.
And... bingo.
Twenty seconds in, and I have them
speaking their wog lingo.
[sighs]
Mr Shelby, I do have plans.
I will have need of men like you.
Except, of course,
there is no other man like you.
You, in particular, I need.
But please.
Don't imagine I would
trouble myself with turf wars.
You have many enemies.
Shuffle the pack and pick another card.
That investigation
of the dead journalist, the queer...
I've made that go away.
Read it and, er, come back to me.
Next time, bring only an open mind
and a cigar to celebrate our union.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Tommy exhales]
[clears throat]
What the fuck was that all about, Tom?
Fuck.
-[Arthur breathing heavily]
-[Tommy] Arthur!
Do not let them get inside your head.
That's exactly how these people work.
Who the fuck are these people?
Hmm?
Who the fuck are they?
[smacks lips]
[sighs] I've just been invited...
[clears throat]
...to become the deputy leader
of a brand-new political party.
[smacks lips]
These people say they are the future.
[Arthur breathing heavily]
Do you want a drink?
I've stopped.
So, what have you decided?
I've been talking to the Friends.
What friends?
Quakers. Friends who meet
at the Meeting House in Bournville.
I'm staying in Bournville.
[Lizzie] And what do they say?
They say I have been led astray.
If you've come to talk about redemption,
you're talking to the wrong person.
I also went to a solicitor.
They heard my name was Shelby,
and suddenly, they were too busy.
To divorce a Shelby man,
you have to go to a solicitor in London.
I found one.
He said he'd represent me.
But I put the phone down.
Not through fear.
I chose this life, it didn't choose me.
Also, Lizzie, one of the Friends is a man.
He listens to me when I talk.
His wife died of the Spanish flu.
He has a daughter.
And you're considering
making this daughter an orphan.
Nothing has happened.
Nor will it.
He would die without his eyes.
And out of kindness,
Tommy would offer his daughter
a place in one of his institutions
for orphaned girls.
Or even take her into the family.
And it would begin again.
What is the thing, Linda?
The thing you can't put aside?
It's not Arthur.
It's who I am when he's there.
God hears every filthy word in my head,
knows every dirty thing.
And your Friends don't use filthy words?
If I fall this time,
I'll fall all the way.
Perhaps it's what you deserve
with your filthy words.
[Lizzie chuckles]
I used to fuck seven men a day,
and now I'm learning
how to ride a horse side-saddle.
There's good and there's evil.
There's both mixed.
And that's Arthur and you and me.
You don't get what you deserve,
you get what you take.
What about him?
[Lizzie] He's making up his mind.
[footsteps approaching]
[door opens]
Someone called Polly Gray to see you.
Yes or no?
Yes.
[footsteps receding]
[footsteps approaching]
[Ada] I've come to take you to the clinic.
I already told Michael.
My husband or no one.
I've got a car.
They have taxis.
Even in this fucking city.
Look, if they don't hear a heartbeat,
they're gonna give you options.
None of them are nice.
I had my check-up three days ago.
They heard a beating heart.
But if they had told me
that baby had died inside of me,
I would have wanted someone with me.
My husband may do as he's told, but, er...
I don't.
Look, if they hear a heartbeat,
you won't need anybody with you,
'cause you'll have the baby with you.
So I will leave you alone.
But if you get in a taxi in this city
and they hear your accent,
they'll take you on a grand tour.
Come on.
[Karl] So, when will Mum be home?
[Younger] She said
she had to go to Birmingham.
Do you want me to cook you something?
Cook?
You're a man.
[Younger] This is really not fair.
Your mother never told me
you were this good.
I'm in a club. I'm champion.
I've beat people even older than you.
Even older than me?
[scoffs]
At school, some of the children say
that black people and Jews are worse.
Worse than what?
Than anything.
And one teacher, Mr Hudson,
he calls my friend "the little Jew boy."
[breathes deeply]
Karl,
these days,
there are some very stupid people
saying some very stupid things.
Okay?
What do you think?
Checkmate.
I think I don't want you to be my dad...
'cause my dad's white and he's in heaven.
[footsteps receding]
[Polly] I came to see you in hospital
to tell you there is a strategy in place.
Not to break you out.
[Aberama] Don't worry.
My sister will look after me.
You must stay here,
and you'll let Tommy deal with the men
who killed your son.
You're 45 today?
I'm probably a bit older than that.
Probably.
I've dealt death.
Now death has dealt with me.
I have one more killing to do,
then I'll be done.
Happy birthday, Polly Gray.
[Aberama and woman greeting in Romani]
[Aberama grunts]
[engine starts]
Get a car and a driver.
Find out where the Fury family are camped.
I need their men to help me.
I need my hunting rifle, 50 bullets.
I'm going to Scotland...
tonight.
[door unlocks]
[Younger] I was expecting Ada.
Yeah. Give you a key, did she?
I was meant to meet her today,
but she said she had to go to Birmingham.
Yes, Tommy sent her on a mission.
She's doing my job for me.
Where's Karl, eh? Where's the boy?
He went to buy an ice cream.
Ada said to tell you she'd be late.
[Younger] You knew I'd be here?
Yeah. We knew you'd be here.
We have some business for you.
[Michael snorting]
[exhales]
Any business I have with you, Mr Shelby,
is meant to be strictly confidential.
Er, Michael, you still have
shit on your shoes.
My associate here can evidently smell it.
I don't mean any offence.
Here, Michael. Go and find Karl
and buy him an ice cream, eh?
The man doesn't trust you.
Fuck you, Tom.
You know, Gina phoned.
Baby's heart's beating strong.
But I swear to God, Tom,
by the time that baby
draws his first breath,
-you and I will be done.
-[Tommy scoffs]
And you will be king.
Is that it, Michael?
You know, Tom,
there are doctors in London now
who can talk their way into your head.
Dig out all the shit.
Perhaps you should see one.
[coughs]
You're still not alone.
Me brother and I are the same person.
Here.
There's a letter from Mosley.
You should read it.
What investigation is he talking about?
Two weeks ago,
a journalist was killed in Maida Vale.
The night before,
he'd come to me about some story
he was going to write about me.
We had nothing to do with that killing.
[Younger] Mosley wants you as his deputy?
His constituency is Smethwick.
It borders me own.
And he wants Birmingham as his stronghold.
He knows I have strong support
among working people.
We help him out with rallies,
and show up at some town hall meetings.
Right, and why are you
showing this letter to me?
A Minister of State...
who may have seditious intentions.
There's no proof of sedition
in this letter.
[Tommy] You work in intelligence, Younger.
You don't need proof.
Give it to your superiors.
Mr Shelby, I have a very specific brief.
My brief is specifically
to gather information
on the activities of communists.
Your immediate superior
in the intelligence unit
is a Colonel Patrick Wyatt, yeah?
I understand he regularly plays polo
with Oswald Mosley.
They share membership of various clubs
in London and Birmingham.
[Younger] I have specific orders.
I am a soldier. I--
You think you can join this family?
I have no intention of joining a family.
Oh, thank fuck for that,
'cause, er, you'd hate our weddings.
I thought you said
this was about business.
Yes. Family business
and government business.
All in one envelope.
Younger...
listen to me. Forget about Ada.
Forget about weddings.
You know what Mosley represents.
You know his philosophy.
Now, I'm planning to reply to him
and tell him that I'm making up me mind.
But in the meantime,
you need to give me instruction.
I could fight him on me own if I have to,
or I could join his organisation
and undermine him on behalf of the King.
But you need to make a decision.
[exhales heavily]
[sighs]
[smacks lips]
I suppose there are a few things
I can do on my own initiative.
[door opens]
[exhales]
[objects clatter]
On your fucking feet.
[breathing heavily]
Hello, Tom.
I thought you were staying over in London.
Hello, Johnny.
How are you, eh?
[door closes]
How are your ribs?
Are you managing?
-Just about, Tom, yeah.
-Yeah? Good.
And who's that?
Is it Maisy or is it Clara?
Ah.
Sandra.
Well, may I say,
your breakfasts...
are a great improvement.
[shakily] Mr Shelby,
I'm sorry.
Don't worry, Sandra.
The only way to get fired
from this household is through burnt toast
or talking to the police.
Go on, go to bed.
And, Sandra...
everything Johnny said is lies.
-[scoffs]
-[door opens]
-Johnny, Johnny, Johnny.
-[door closes]
While you was gone, I got a message, Tom.
A cousin of Aberama Gold.
Galloped from Meriden.
He said Aberama wants you to know
that he's gone to Scotland
to deal with his business himself,
and that you'd know what that meant.
Fuck!
The boy said Aberama arrived
from the hospital in Polly's Bentley.
She fucking helped him?
[chuckles]
She fucking helped him.
But it can't be love, 'cause it's Polly.
'Cause it's fucking Polly.
[sighs] All right, Johnny,
I have a job for you.
Tom, I'm in a lot of pain here.
I need you to go and find Aberama Gold.
He has kin on the Lothian border.
The Fury family.
For fuck's sake, Tom!
The Furys,
they don't even use words to fucking talk.
Just hand gestures and fucking howls.
You will go to them and you will find him.
-Tom, I am in fucking pain here.
-Yeah, you appear to be managing.
I said I was just managing.
Well, you can just manage
to sit in a car with Arthur
and follow the patrin
to find the Fury family.
Arthur will take care of everything
that requires bones and muscles.
I warned you, Tom.
The Golds will be the death of one of us.
[door closes]
And it looks like
it's going to be fucking me! Ow!
Well, go on.
Open it.
[Polly] So...
you heard the baby's heartbeat today.
[chuckles]
Beats so fast.
Would have been a birthday gift enough.
New life.
[Gina] Liberty.
Freedom.
Feels like a weapon.
I only came because
Michael's driving back from London,
and he said he didn't want you
to be on your own.
So...
whose idea was the gift of freedom?
Mine.
You want to take Michael
and the baby to New York?
Yes.
The baby will have two grandmothers.
The other one lives--
The other one lives amongst human beings.
The other one is a human being.
-[Gina sighs]
-It's all right,
I'm not drunk.
I'm just free.
So, what do you want?
My approval?
Your help.
Michael wants you to come with us.
We can all live in Long Island,
right on the beach.
Isn't Long Island in Australia?
Or is it in California
amongst the Indians?
It's in New York,
Polly.
You see, we all try and get away.
But we never do.
I wish I felt that heartbeat today.
You're starting to sound
a little sorry for yourself.
I'm an American.
We don't just go round and round
and round. We go in a straight line.
And my baby...
will be born in New York.
[door opens]
[door closes]
I'm not happy about moving this meeting
to licensed premises.
You've saved your union the train fare,
and you hate London anyway.
We are looking for popular speakers
for our upcoming rally.
You're making quite a name for yourself
in the Commons.
Betty!
-What are you drinking?
-Water.
Bottle of champagne, Betty.
You'll drink it on your own.
[Tommy] That's the idea.
Shall we sit down, Miss Eden?
[grunts]
Revolution.
So, how is life as a socialist?
This glass...
The bubbles...
They rise to the top.
Each bubble has the same chance to rise.
That's a very peculiar form of socialism.
And this bottle...
Once the cork comes out,
you can't get it back in.
You need to finish what you started.
It's cleverness, that's all.
So, you're playing at this?
Yeah, people can be turned around.
-Even your people.
-My people?
Yeah.
For them, it's just the same.
Communism, fascism.
For most people,
it's an apple and an apple.
Fascism is the subject of the rally.
I want you to speak against it.
In answer to your question,
I cannot address your rally...
because it's not part of
the current strategy.
Are you okay, Thomas?
Do you want a man to carry you home?
[glass tumbles]
I knew we should not have had this meeting
on licensed premises.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Grace] Happy or sad, Thomas?
I warn you...
I'll break your heart.
[Tommy coughs]
I didn't expect you home.
Frances said Linda was here today.
Frances has a very specific loyalty,
doesn't she?
Well,
people are loyal
to those who pay their wages.
Also, Maggie at the exchange
said you made some calls.
Then you'll know I called a solicitor.
Did Maggie listen in to the conversation?
He said he'd represent me.
But I put the phone down.
There and then, I made a decision.
And when I heard your car pull up,
I got changed.
You said in your head,
you still pay for it.
So I have decided to continue
to take the payment
and balance my heart against my head
as though it were a book of accounts.
Value my head a shilling more.
[Tommy chuckles]
When was the last time
you had to worry about shillings?
Eh?
People are loyal to those
who pay their wages.
So I will be loyal to you.
But this is the deal.
You don't fuck anybody else in my house.
Nor within a day of holding our child
by the hand. A day on either side.
And you let me in sometimes.
Into your head.
To clear it out.
That what needs clearing out.
Agreed.
And this...
always.
[Tommy] The deal is,
you belong to me.
My property.
No one touches my property.
I touch myself, but it's still you anyway,
so that's why I put the phone down.
No, Tom.
We do it in the bed at least.
[both breathing heavily and moaning]
[chuckles]
[whispers] Everything is mine, Lizzie.
Everything.
[Lizzie moaning]
[phone ringing]
[grunts]
[line rings]
[line connects]
[Tommy] Arthur?
-Yeah?
-Frances was right.
Linda was here today.
[grunts] Fuck.
What did she say, huh?
I just want to talk to her, that's all.
Arthur, listen. First I need you
to go to Scotland
and bring back Aberama Gold.
Then we'll go and we'll find Linda.
No, no, no.
I'll keep calling you, Tom.
You know I will.
I'll call this number back.
Again, again, and again.
If you do not answer,
I'll jump in my fucking car
and I'll drive to your house.
You know I will.
I'll stay there all night if I have to.
I won't go nowhere.
Not Scotland, until you tell me
what it is you know.
[sighs]
[Tommy] All right, listen to me.
I don't have an address.
But she's with the Quakers in Bournville.
Apparently, there is someone
who is a Friend.
He had a wife who died...
from Spanish flu in 1918.
He has a daughter.
That should be enough to find him.
And Arthur,
just talk to him
and get a message to Linda.
Nothing happened, Arthur.
He's a Quaker who is a friend.
They're not like us, they talk.
Oh, I'll speak to him. Hmm.
Man to man.
And then after that,
I'll go up north, hmm.
Deal with our business. I promise ya.
Arthur. Arthur, listen to me...
[door closes]
[Lizzie] Who were you talking to?
I have to ask you 'cause Maggie
at the exchange won't tell me.
Who was it?
Was it Arthur?
[inhales sharply]
I need me brother in one piece.
Arthur makes his own decisions.
You marry a Shelby,
you stay fucking married.
-[door opens]
-[Lizzie] Fuck.
[door closes]
Well, look at this, hmm?
Can I help you?
Yeah, I think you can.
I'm looking for Linda Shelby.
Do you know her?
Eh?
I'm Arthur...
her husband.
If you're her husband,
she doesn't want to talk to you.
Well, look at you.
[chuckles]
Ain't you smart?
Eh?
What, you got all the fucking answers,
have ya?
Well, let's try you with another one, huh?
Let's try you with another one.
How about...
How about we search
for the fucking truth within, hmm?
Let's have a look, all right?
Let's have a look.
Let's see what we've got inside here, eh?
-Inside, you fucking bastard!
-[groaning]
[Arthur] Hey...
you wanna keep looking, eh?
♪ She'll go ♪
♪ She'll lay belief on you ♪
[man whimpering]
[grunting and groaning]
♪ How can life become her point of view ♪
♪ And when the clothes are strewn ♪
♪ Don't be afraid of the room ♪
♪ Touch the fullness of her breast ♪
♪ Feel the love of her caress... ♪
-[Arthur] Hey...
-[groaning]
I will ask you again.
Eh? Eh?
I'll ask you again. Come here,
listen, listen. Get up.
Where is she?
Eh?
[man] No.
[Arthur] Eh.
[man] No. No, no, no!
♪ She will be your living end ♪
[knife slashes]
[indistinct shouting]
[Arthur breathing heavily]
[chuckles]
I'm a good man.
I'm a fucking good man like you.
[sobbing]
A God-fearing man.
And there's good in my heart.
There is good in my heart!
But my hands...
These hands belong to the devil.
The fucking devil!
[crying and sniffling]
Right. I...
[Strong] Did she come back?
No.
[Strong] Is she in Scotland?
Is that why you're going?
No, she's not
in fucking Scotland, Charlie.
Whiskey. We want whiskey.
Maps. Cigars.
Load the van. We want it all.
Who's "we"?
Me and Johnny Dogs.
Ah.
So it's you and Johnny Dogs
against Scotland.
You know, at the BSA,
our friends could get you
some of them new artillery cannons
that fire ten shells a second.
You can mount one
on the roof of your fucking car.
Petrol.
Need petrol.
It's so far up north,
they run out of the bloody stuff.
Yeah.
Still riding around on fucking chariots,
they are.
Curly, Arthur is going to Scotland,
so he needs hand grenades.
[Curly] How many?
Fuck's sake, it's like it's normal.
[hesitantly] Our friends at the BSA
still have lots left from the war,
but we can't give them away, yeah?
Get me some hand grenades, Curly, eh?
-Hmm?
-[chuckles nervously]
You find them back there, eh?
Good boy, yeah?
Go get me some.
-Put them on my account.
-Yeah.
[whispers] How many?
Three, Curly.
Three, three. Right, yeah.
Find a way of getting her back, Arthur.
Without her,
you're as good as dead already.
That's them. The Billy Boys.
Gentlemen,
you have just crossed the border
into the County of East Tollcross.
Now, according to
the unwritten constitution
of Tollcross County,
Gypsies, Catholics,
and other criminally-minded individuals
are not allowed to work the roads
of our Protestant district,
on account of the poor quality
of their labour.
So, my own boys
will be taking over from here.
We will be needing your tools,
your tar, your burner,
and your transportation.
You're Gypsies.
You can easily steal another.
I have the keys to the truck.
[keys jingling]
[groans]
[men grunting and groaning]
-[bones cracking]
-[screaming]
Now...
I want you boys to take a message
back to Jimmy McCavern.
"You killed my son.
-You hoisted him on a cross!"
-[groans]
In this gun...
there is a bullet.
And on it is carved the name McCavern.
And when the time comes
for his crucifixion,
it will be me who drives in the nails!
[screaming]
Mr Shelby!
At last you are alone.
I think we'll make quite the team.
The pheasants won't know what hit them.
-[wings flapping]
-[gunshots]
You're a fine shot, Mr Shelby.
You were in the yeomanry, yes?
You were cavalry.
You won the Distinguished Service medal.
That will help.
With what?
Two months ago, I was in Rome.
I met Mr Mussolini.
You and I, and men like him...
[wings flapping]
...we will shape the future.
When will you resign
from the Labour party?
The day before I announce
the formation of my new party.
The British Union of Fascists will be born
on January the 1st of next year.
First day of a new decade.
The 1930s, Mr Shelby, will belong to us.
Did you bring that cigar?
Before we smoke,
I have some conditions.
It really isn't going to be
that kind of relationship.
Just smoke like the fine man
you will become.
[bell tolling]
Yes, Colonel Ben Younger.
I have an allocated confidential line.
Code 78.
[breathes deeply]
It's me. [clears throat]
I've agreed to work with our friend.
He is going to announce on January 1st.
I need to know that my position
as informant against him
is officially sanctioned.
[band playing]
Today, gentlemen,
we are avenging an unprovoked attack
on members of our organisation
who were simply carrying out
a routine border patrol.
Our enemies are Gypsies,
members of a race
destined for natural eradication anyway,
due to what the scientists call selection.
And since these beggars are unchristened
and unregistered,
the local constabulary will as soon
drop them in a communal grave
as find a name for a gravestone.
So, proceed in any manner you choose
to find the fugitive we seek.
[band playing in distance]
[gun cocks]
[gasps]
Morning, Mr Gold.
Yeah,
the Billy Boys are coming for you.
How the fuck'd you find me?
How the fuck did they find me?
I kinda let it slip.
Give you no choice.
What? Hmm? What?
No.
In the Bentley outside,
the engine running.
Fastest engine in the world apparently,
which is good.
We got two minutes to get out of here.
We are officers of
the East Lanarkshire Special Constabulary.
We are seeking a man
by the name of Aberama Gold.
Hand the gentleman over,
and no one else will be harmed.
Fuck! Take cover!
[screaming]
[grunting]
[McCavern] So, Tommy Shelby.
[sniffs]
It's war you want...
it's war you shall have.
[theme song playing]
♪ On a gathering storm
Comes a tall handsome man ♪
♪ In a dusty black coat
With a red right hand ♪
♪ A shadow is cast wherever he stands ♪
♪ Stacks of green paper
In his red right hand ♪